Muhammad Arslan

Full Stack Mobile Application Developer (Flutter and Node is)

Passionate Software Engineer with more than 3 years of experience, dedicated to transforming complex problems into innovative tech solutions. Focused on user needs in mobile apps domain, eager to meet demanding development objectives.

maherarslan325@gmail.com



+923039478325



in linkedin.com/in/arslan325



github.com/arslan325

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Flutter & Node js Developer NextTier

08/2022 - Present

Islamabad

Role & Responsibility

- Developing cross-platform mobile applications
- Implementing beautiful & responsive designs
- Working on MVC, MVVM & Bloc architectures
- Developing robust and efficient RESTful APIs using Node.is
- Designing and implementing a real-time backend using Socket.io
- · Participating in sprint plaining & task management
- Participating in code reviews & improvement of code
- Implemented deep links, Crashlytics, auth, realtime database & Firestore in Firebase
- Worked on Github actions for automated build distribution with Firebase
- Distributed apps on google Play Store and App Store

Flutter Developer EoriSoft

10/2021 - 07/2022

Islamabad

Role & Responsibility

- Implemented high-quality, responsive Flutter designs.
- Worked on Google map feature
- Solved crashes and errors
- o Utilized Dart language to develop clean, maintainable, and efficient code.
- Collaborated with back-end developers to ensure seamless integration of functionalities.
- Implemented recommended code practices

Flutter & Wordpress Developer

Fiverr

08/2020 - Present

Role & Responsibility

• Implemented UI/UX designs into Flutter applications.

EDUCATION

BS(HONS) Computer Science

Federal urdu university of art, science & Technology, Islamabad

2017 - 2021 3.75 CGPA

SKILLS



PROJECTS

CC APP

 CCAPP is the realtime game app that multiplayer wants to play collectively to discussed on any topics and won tokens. This project is in development phase.

Quiz App (App and Backend)

• The quiz app is also a real-time single or multiplayer app that multiplayer plays as a team to solve questions and won prizes. This project is in the development phase.

Follow Elvis

- The Follow Elvis App presents 200+ episodes about Elvis and his time in text, audio, photos and film.
- App store link: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=com.follow.elvis

• Ehjezly is an appointment booking app that allows the patients to book an appointment according to their suitable times.

Cafe IO

Event Booking App

CFOA

• CFOA is an e-commerce app that allows the users to order furniture according to their own custom designs.

LANGUAGES

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Puniabi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Photography

Exploring new things

Movies